{
    "subject": "Michael_Gallant",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Neela_Rasgotra",
    "human_readable": "Michael Gallant is married to Neela Rasgotra.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9245808124542236,
            "question": "To whom is Neela Rasgotra married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.918345034122467,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Michael Gallant and Neela Rasgotra?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9106941819190979,
            "question": "Is Neela Rasgotra married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8566232919692993,
            "question": "Who is Michael Gallant married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8185679316520691,
            "question": "Name the person Michael Gallant is in a marriage with."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7907878756523132,
            "question": "Are Michael Gallant and Neela Rasgotra partners?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7741623520851135,
            "question": "Who is Michael Gallant's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.633300244808197,
            "question": "What is the name of Michael Gallant's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.09135296195745468,
            "question": "Can you identify the husband in the given statement about a marriage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.0906052365899086,
            "question": "Who are the individuals in a marital relationship according to the given statement?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Michael Gallant is married to Neela Rasgotra.",
            "html": "yago_25575_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you identify the husband in the given statement about a marriage?",
            "html": "yago_25575_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Michael Gallant's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_25575_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Michael Gallant's wife?",
            "html": "yago_25575_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25575_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25575_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25575_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25575_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25575_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25575_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25575_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25575_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25575_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25575_87.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The documents mention that Dr. Michael Gallant and Dr. Neela Rasgotra are a married couple, and they even have a child together."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Dr. Michael Gallant (portrayed by Sharif Atkins) was married to Dr. Neela Rasgotra (portrayed by Parminder Nagra). Therefore, the triple \"Michael Gallant is married to Neela Rasgotra\" is supported by the information provided in the context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}